{
    "question": "B. Write a,b, or c ( Tulislah a,b atau c)!    1. My hobby is ... (Memasak)\r\n2. Two mother is meaning ...\r\n3. Teacher How are you?\r\nStudent\r\nThank you\r\n4. Anggur is\r\n5. Cat eats\r\n6. I like playing football\r\nFootball is\r\n7. Empat pisang kuning is.\r\n8. Indonesian flag is ..... And\r\n9. Teacher Riri is my English\r\n(Guru)\r\n10. Father is\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> 1. Cooking</p><p></p><p>2. Step mother / second mother</p><p></p><p>3. I&#039;m fine, thank you</p><p></p><p>4. Grape</p><p></p><p>5. Fish</p><p></p><p>6. Sepakbola</p><p></p><p>7. There are four yellow banana</p><p></p><p>8. Red and white</p><p></p><p>9. Guru</p><p></p><p>10. Ayah</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "what-does-the-song-talk-about-756",
            "question": "What does the song talk about\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>which song? lagu yang mana? kamu ga nambahin lagu apa apa</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>artinya:apa yang dibicarakan lagu itu</p><p>nahh jawabannya gak tau harusnya tambahin foto</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "last-saturday-my-sister-dina-did-something-funny-she-got-up-ve-403",
            "question": "Last Saturday, my sister Dina, did    something funny. She got up very late, at\r\nsix. She ran fast to the bathroom. She took\r\nvery quick bath, got dressed, took her bag,\r\nand ran off to school. She did not even have\r\nbreakfast. After walking for five minutes,\r\nshe noticed that no other children were\r\ngoing to school. Soon she realized it was\r\nSaturday! So she walked back home. We\r\nlaughed at her when she got home. She also\r\nlaughed at herself.\r\n8. Whatkind of the text is it?\r\na. Recount text\r\nb. Descriptive text\r\nc. Narrative text\r\nd. Procedure text\r\n9. The purpose of the text is ...?\r\na. Entertain the readers\r\nb. Describe something\r\nc. Tell past event\r\nd. How to make something\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>8. A. recount text</p><p>9. C. tell past event</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu, maap kalo salah. Kalo bener jangan lupa jadikan jawaban tercerdas yak\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>8.a recount text maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "teks-iklan-mie-goreng-dalam-bahasa-inggris-720",
            "question": "Teks iklan mie goreng dalam bahasa inggris\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>fried noodle ad text kek gitu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B.indonesia: Iklan mie goreng</p><p></p><p>Terjemahan b.inggris: Fried noodle advertisement</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p><h3>Semoga bermanfaat dan membantu;)</h3>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "22-you-my-dictionaries-right-now-a-are-bringing-374",
            "question": "22. ......you ......my dictionaries right now?    a. are : bringing d. are : bring\r\n\r\nb. is : bringing e. am : bring\r\n\r\nc. was : bringing\r\n\r\n23. Budi and I ..... Working in big company.\r\n\r\na. am b. Is c. are d. were e. was\r\n\r\n24. You ....swimming now\r\n\r\na. isn't b. hadn't c. hasn't d. aren't e. wasn't\r\n\r\n25. ....you sleeping?\r\n\r\na. isn't b. Am c. are d. was e. will\r\n\r\n26. Under = ...... (synonim)\r\n\r\na. below b. Up c. beside d. left e. right\r\n\r\n27. Powerfull =......(synonim)\r\n\r\na. Soft b. Fast c. stupid d. strong e. false\r\n\r\n28. Excellent =......(synonim)\r\n\r\na. Full b. Hot c. bad d. sick e. very good\r\n\r\n29. Great =....(synonim)\r\n\r\na. Big b. Deep c. easy d. strike e. rich\r\n\r\n30. Food =.....(synonim)\r\n\r\na. Dead b. same c. lose d. meal e. light\r\n\r\n31. Sharp x ....... (antonym)\r\n\r\na. Dull b. small c. dirty d. cold e. hate\r\n\r\n32. Start x ....... (antonym)\r\n\r\na. Stop b. Enter c. bad d. enemy e. stupid\r\n\r\n33. Clean x ....... (antonym)\r\n\r\na. Lose b. Dirty c. near d. plus e. even\r\n\r\n34. Sell x ....... (antonym)\r\n\r\na. Buy b. Short c. dead d. left e. east\r\n\r\n35. Slow x ......(antonym)\r\n\r\na. Fast b. False c. full d. tall e. easy\r\n\r\n36. Four times six is......\r\n\r\na. twenty four c. twenty three e. twenty eight\r\n\r\nb. twenty two d. twenty one\r\n\r\n37. A thousand divided by........is two hundred and \r\n\r\nfifty \r\n\r\na. Four b . five c. three d. ten e. seven\r\n\r\n38. Twenty five minus two is......\r\n\r\na. twenty three c. twenty e. twenty two\r\n\r\nb. thirty d. fourteen\r\n\r\n39. Two hundred divided by four is.....\r\n\r\na. fifteen c. fourteen e. fourty\r\n\r\nb. fifty d. thirty\r\n\r\n40. One hundred and twenty plus thirty is......\r\n\r\na. one hundred and thirty\r\n\r\nb. one hundred and seventy\r\n\r\nc. one hundred and fourty\r\n\r\nd. one hundred and eighty\r\n\r\ne. one hundred and fifty\r\n\r\n41. 345 means.....\r\n\r\na. three hundred and fourty\r\n\r\nb. thirty four and two\r\n\r\nc. three hundred and fourty two\r\n\r\nd. three hundred fourty and two\r\n\r\ne. three hundred dan thirty two\r\n\r\n42. 2.586 means......\r\n\r\na. two thousand five hundred and sixty eight\r\n\r\nb. two thousand hundred \r\n\r\nc. five thousand and sixty eight\r\n\r\nd. two thousand five hundred sixty eight\r\n\r\ne. two thousand and five hundred sixty eight\r\n\r\n43. 47 + 69 = 116\r\n\r\na. fourty seven plus sixty nine equal one \r\n\r\nhundred and sixteen \r\n\r\nb. fourty seven plus sixty nine equal one \r\n\r\nhundred and sixty\r\n\r\nc. fourty seven plus ninety six equal one \r\n\r\nhundred and sixteen\r\n\r\nd. fourty seven plus sixty four equal one \r\n\r\nhundred\r\n\r\ne. fourty seven plus sixty nine equal one \r\n\r\nhundred sixteen\r\n\r\n44. One hundred and thirty three minus twenty two \r\n\r\nis......\r\n\r\na. one hundred and twelve\r\n\r\nb. one hundred and ten\r\n\r\nc. one hundred eleven\r\n\r\nd. one hundred and eleven\r\n\r\ne. one hundred and eight\r\n\r\n45. Wendy isn't a clever boy any more ,because he \r\n\r\nis now very......he cann't answer all the \r\n\r\nquestions in the test.\r\n\r\na. diligent c. lazy e. beautiful\r\n\r\nb. stupid d. smart\r\n\r\n46. 3 : 00 am, What time is it?\r\n\r\na. it's three past three\r\n\r\nb. it's three past\r\n\r\nc. it's three to\r\n\r\nd. it's three to five\r\n\r\ne. it's three o'clock\r\n\r\n47. 9 : 05 pm, What time is it?\r\n\r\na. it's nine past five\r\n\r\nb. it's five past nine\r\n\r\nc. it's nine to five\r\n\r\nd. it's nine past three\r\n\r\ne. it's nine o'clock\r\n\r\n48. 12 : 30 am, What time is it?\r\n\r\na. it's a half to twelve\r\n\r\nb. it's a half past twelve\r\n\r\nc. it's a half past one\r\n\r\nd. it's a half to one\r\n\r\ne. it's a half past two\r\n\r\n49. 11 : 45 pm, What time is it?\r\n\r\na. it's a quarter past twelve\r\n\r\nb. it's twelve past quarter\r\n\r\nc. it's a quarter to twelve\r\n\r\nd. it's twelve to a quarter\r\n\r\ne. it's a quarter o'clock\r\n\r\n50. 5 : 40 pm, What time is it?\r\n\r\na. it's six past one\r\n\r\nb. it's six past twenty\r\n\r\nc. it's twenty to five\r\n\r\nd. it's five past twenty\r\n\r\ne. it's twenty to six\r\n\r\ntolong bantuin dong kak\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>22. a. are : bringing d. are : bring</p><p>23.c. are</p><p>24.d. aren&#039;t</p><p>25.c. are</p><p>26.a. below</p><p>27d. strong</p><p>28.e. very good</p><p>29.a. Big</p><p>30.d. meal</p><p>31.a. Dull</p><p>32.a. Stop</p><p>33.b. Dirty</p><p>34.a. Buy</p><p>35.a. Fast</p><p>36.a. twenty four</p><p>37b . five</p><p>38a. twenty three</p><p>39.b. fifty</p><p>40e. one hundred and fifty</p><p>41. yg bener three hundred and fourty five</p><p>42 yg bener two thousand five hundred and eighty six</p><p>43 \u00a0e. fourty seven plus sixty nine equal one hundred sixteen</p><p>44 d. one hundred and eleven</p><p>45 b. stupid</p><p>46 e. it&#039;s three o&#039;clock</p><p>47 a. it&#039;s nine past five</p><p>48d. it&#039;s a half to one</p><p>49c. it&#039;s a quarter to twelve</p><p>50 e. it&#039;s twenty to six</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalo ada yang salah, semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "b-qsc-d-gl-i-have-a-favorite-bancherh-my-school-he-is-mr-denl-656",
            "question": "B    QSC\r\nD. GL\r\nI have a favorite bancherh my school He is Mr. Denl. He is\r\nmy English facher. He is 30 years old. He is tall and\r\nhandsome. He has round eyes a pointed nose, and thick lips\r\nHe has straight har that always looks neat. He is the strict\r\nand discipline person. He also has bng mustache and beard\r\nfairy dense. His sun is brown. He is very diligent. He is also\r\nsmart and honest He oves must very much. He is very good\r\nat playing a guitar. He is a good person and we bve him very\r\nmuch\r\n\r\n12. How does he look like?\r\nA He has found eyes a flat nose, and thin lips. He has\r\nstraight hair\r\nB He hasslanteyes a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has\r\nC. He has found eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He\r\nhas straight hair\r\nD. He has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thin lips. He has\r\ny hair\r\n13 How does he look like?\r\nA He has found eyes a fet nose, and thin lips. He has\r\nstraight hair\r\nB He has slant eyes a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has\r\nWavy hair\r\nC. He has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lps. He\r\nhas straight hair\r\nD. He has found eyes, a pointed nose, and thin lips. He has\r\n14.Deb\r\ncoo\r\nMrs\r\nis his skin brown?\r\nA Yes it's\r\nB No. is not\r\nC Yes. It does\r\nD. No. he is not\r\n15 What do you think about Mr. Dent?\r\nA He is very digort smart and honest person\r\nB Hois smart honest but lay person\r\nCHe is the strict but not discipline person\r\nD He is smart toucher but not discipline person\r\n16 A place where alrcraft magularly take off and land, with\r\nbuildings for passengers to waith\r\nA Gas Station\r\nB Train station\r\nC Arport\r\n17 Parking Ama many people standing outside the movie\r\nA There is\r\nB There are\r\nC There\r\nD Is there\r\n18 then a small cat playing with some toys\r\nA is\r\nB Are\r\nC Am\r\nD. Have\r\n19 We use this thing to cook our meals tsa\r\nA Basin\r\nB Stove\r\nC Rack\r\nD Knife\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>12. C. he has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has straight hair</p><p>13. C. he has round eyes, a pointed nose, and thick lips. He has straight hair</p><p>14. C. yes it does</p><p>15. A. he is very diligent, smart, and honest person</p><p>16. C. airport</p><p>17. B. there are</p><p>18. A. is</p><p>19. B. stove</p><p></p><p><strong>Semoga</strong><strong> </strong><strong>terbantu</strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>maap</strong><strong> </strong><strong>kalo</strong><strong> </strong><strong>salah</strong><strong>\u270c</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "if-hehe-will-get-hiher-aim-271",
            "question": "If he...he will get hi/her aim\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>her</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "write-down-the-meaning-of-expression-of-predicting-speculating-an-275",
            "question": "Write down the meaning of expression of predicting speculating and and judging",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Tuliskan arti ungkapan memprediksi berspekulasi dan dan menilai</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "12-they-will-be-here-soon-the-word-they-refers-to-a-nabil-385",
            "question": "12. They will be here soon. The word they refers to ....    A. Nabil and Jaka\r\nB. Jaka and Mrs. Maya\r\nC. Jaka and Gita\r\nD. Erigo and Gita\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C Jaka dan Gita</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "these-are-wild-animals-315",
            "question": "These are wild animals",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>artinya ini adalah hewan liar</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga bermanfaat:)</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pilihan-alat-transportasi-saat-ini-sangat-banyak-alat-transporta-138",
            "question": "Pilihan alat transportasi saat ini sangat banyak. Alat transportasi yang paling tepat    dipilih ketika bepergian jauh lintas pulau adalah .... dibantu ya kak\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Pesawat</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu ya kak...</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>kapal dan pesawat</p><p></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}